One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Who goes there?
Hey!
This thing just talked!
D-D-Don't be ridiculous! You must have imagined it!
Really?
It's hard enough to believe
that this is actually a dragon!
Is it really a dragon?
Yes, as hard as it is to believe.
A lizard's body with giant wings...
No matter how you look at it,
it's exactly what the legends describe!
Don't tell me...
I-I-I-
It breathed fire!
How could a creature like this possibly exist?!
Am I dreaming?!
How interesting!
It wasn't effective?!
He sure is tough!
Behind you!
Luffy!
It's looking right at us!
Bring it on!
It can hear you!
I can sense your presence!
So it's true. The dragon definitely just said something!
Ultimate Tiger Hunt
Damn it! How can it be so strong and tough?!
Bastard!
Luffy!
Yeah?
He spoke.
Told you so!
I heard it too! Why?!
It's flying!
Pffft! Are you companions of that Warlord?!
Hot!
It's so hot... and that dragon just spoke again!
He said "Warlord", right?
Does he have some grudge against the Seven Warlords?
Luffy.
Leave him to me.
This time, I will cut him in half!
Right, I got it!
In that case...
Hot! Hot! Hot!
I'll knock him down to the ground!
Even his body is hot!
Poooh- I must say, this is pleasantly cool!
Poooh- The flames are quite refreshing -pooh!
Ah... Stop that...
That tickles, it does!
Cease this!
I command you to cease this, I do -poooh!
I knew it!
Hey! This is incredible!
There's a human sticking out of the dragon's back!
Huuuh?! What's going on?!
So the one speaking earlier was...
You bastard!
Eat wings, why don't you!
Dumbass!
Zoro! He's falling to you!
Usopp!
Alright!
Sure-Kill Green Star
One-Sword Style
Draw-and-Resheathe Technique
Death Lion Song
Incredible!
This dragon looks delicious!
We can barbecue it on the island's flames!
Great idea!
Nami-swan!
This time, I thought I'd make us a cold shellfish crêpe!
Along with some champagne!
Huh? Are you sleeping?
Mist?
No...
Damn it! I've already inhaled a lot of it!
They've all been knocked out by the gas!
Is this a natural gas unique to the New World?
Or has someone boarded the ship?
I hope those four on the island...
have a Baby Snail Phone with them.
I have to... tell them...
Two humans.
One iron man.
And one pet.
Tie them all up!
Yes, Sir!
Pirates are ideal for our purposes.
Even if they go missing, nobody will care.
Let's take them straight to the Master.
Punk Hazard Island
The Burning Lands
Let's pull him out!
I say, who are you?! Unhand me, now -pooh!
Hey! I'm gonna get you out of there!
Hold still!
Heave, ho!
I tore him in half! Sorry!
Idiot, you think apologizing will fix this?!
You've killed him!
Pooh- Am I free now?
The legs are speaking! What's going on?!
Zombie! Monster!
Hang on.
What could this mean?
There's no sign of his body being torn off.
What's up with that?
So... does that mean he was just a pair of legs all along?
What a weirdo!
He's pretty tall.
Who goes there? What are you doing?
I sense your presence,
but I have neither eyes nor ears.
You sure are unique!
Poooh- Though I know not who you are,
you will let me pass!
What?
I will not die here!
He's running away!
You shall not get away with this! Foolish Warlord!
Hey, wait! Join my-
Cut it out, Luffy!
And... that's how it happened?
Yeah, that's right!
This dragon meat is delicious!
What are these things called, Usopp?
Huh?
I guess...
a centaur, right?
I'm a centaur!
This is awesome!
First he was stuck to the dragon, and now to Luffy?
What's up with this guy?!
You give up?
Damn!
I have been attached to something again -pooh!
Grrr... I could just... Let me go -pooh!
That isn't very polite, Luffy.
Really?
What now?
See? Of course he won't just become part of you!
Nobody would be that obedient!
His upper half must be in trouble somewhere!
Give those legs back to their owner!
Don't you have any imagination, Usopp?
This is just the way he is. See?
I see, so he's supposed to be a Legman?
Yeah right! Like hell I can just accept that!
What's your name?
And about this dragon meat...
You're gonna eat most of it anyway,
so you carry it!
Hey, you guys! Come over here!
Oh, Zoro! Did you find them?
The samurai and the guy who got killed?
Look.
Huh? What is it?
A-A snow covered mountain?!
No... a whole mountain of ice?!
The other half of the island, across the lake,
has snow covered mountains!
Yet this side is scorching hot
and covered with active volcanoes!
What's up with this island?!
This solves one mystery.
Mystery?
Oh, right!
The voice on the Snail Phone said it was cold!
Please, help me!
What's wrong?!
It's freezing... Is that you, boss?
My companions keep getting cut down.
The samurai's gonna kill us all!
So the killer samurai and his victims are over there.
This island is so interesting!
It's snowing on that mountain, right?!
And it's so hot here... I wanna eat a snow cone!
Idiot, you're actually going there?!
It'll be way too cold!
Besides, it's too far away!
Let's head back to the ship now.
How troubling. It looks rather cold.
If there are beasts there, we can take their fur coats.
We'll manage somehow.
No we won't! Why are you guys set on going?!
Snow cones!
H-Hey, wait, Luffy!
Ow... What are you-
I saw it! I saw it! I saw it!
A bird! No, a person! Huh?!
It was a person yet a bird!
A bird? A person? Which was it?!
Huh? What're you talking about?
Huh?! Was it a bird or a person?! Zoro?
There's nobody there.
Sanji, what're you so worked up about?
Oh, you're awake?
Take a look around, and you'll understand.
This is terrible, Franky! We've been locked up!
Hey! What is this place?!
Where are we?!
I was on deck eating that giant shellfish dessert,
and then... I can't remember!
This is just a guess,
but it seems likely that someone used sleeping gas...
and captured us while we were unconscious!
What?!
The ship was gassed, there's no doubt about that.
I'm so sorry. If only I'd noticed it sooner...
This is not good.
Are we gonna be sold off?
Are they human traffickers?
But if they got everyone who was on the ship,
where is Brook?
I don't know. We are the only ones here.
They're human traffickers,
so they wouldn't bother with a skeleton, right?
You can't really be called a human either, you know.
Neither can you!
Whatever!
You there.
Did someone just... say something?
No, it wasn't any of us.
You there, do you enjoy a challenge?
In particular, a puzzle!
Did this thing just speak?
What is this?
This thing? How insolent!
What's this?
Huh? An insect?
Is it some new kind of Snail Phone?
There are eight of them! I didn't notice!
I am no pathetic insect!
You do not seem like bad folk...
These are all bits of my face.
Forgive me,
but could you put them back together for me?
Face? Now that you mention it...
This is a mouth, and this is an eye.
Like this?
How's that?!
It's true! It became a face!
No, there are quite a few parts left over!
Isn't it like this?
Well?
Completely wrong!
No no no... This should work.
We're making progress!
Wrong! Wrong!
I wanna try!
You...
Don't play around with other people's faces!
It's done!
It's become a proper face!
I feel some slight discomfort in my jaw and forehead...
but, very well.
I thank you!
A detached head is talking!
Now you notice?!
How can you be alive?! Are you an evil spirit?!
I do not understand either.
I was not reduced to a head by choice.
That fellow used some queer technique.
I thought I would die upon being cut to pieces,
yet I found myself in this state.
To be cut up by the enemy and yet remain alive...
is a disgrace to a warrior!
One. Two.
Three.
And four.
Hello? Did you find them?
Yeah, I did. I'm about to take them out.
Four intruders.
I see.
How exciting.
Be careful, now.
Roger that.
You were cut down by the enemy,
and you're still alive, even as just a head?
How?! I don't get it!
He's like Buggy! How strange.
I wish I could slice open my belly and let my body decay,
but there are things I must do,
even if my greatest failure must be known!
By the way, you... Do you know where we are?
"You"?!
How dare a female address me, a warrior, in such an informal manner?!
Women shall walk three steps behind men and address them with a modest grace!
What was that, you bastard?
You've got some nerve, for a severed head!
You're talking to the ones who put your head back together!
C-Cease this violence!
You're still talking?!
Cease this, woman!
What kind of country do women like this come from?
So rude and self-centered...
However,
you must be deeply grieved
to have been robbed down to your underwear.
I offer my sympathy.
I haven't been stripped!
What?!
This is just fashion!
How lewd! That is nothing but a breast-band, is it not?!
What, you don't like it?
I daresay I do.
Why, you...
Those lecherous eyes!
It is a trap, it is!
I think his skull's been cracked! Doesn't it hurt?
It hurts... It hur... It hurts not!
It is... merely itchy!
I see, so women from other countries wear only breast-bands?
In that case, I quite like it.
Incidentally, who are you people?
I heard that you were dragged here from your ship.
We're pirates.
Pirates?!
You people are pirates?!
That explains your savagery!
I loathe pirates. They make me vomit!
I thought that perhaps it was fate that brought us to this island of ice at the same time,
and that maybe we could escape together.
But regrettably, since you are pirates,
Hey, wait a second.
What do you mean "island of ice"?
This is a burning island, isn't it?
Yeah, that's right! It's a scorching hot island where even the ocean is on fire!
No, wait.
You...
say that this is an island of ice, right?
Haven't you heard the volcanic eruptions?
I have heard the sound of explosions from time to time,
but I came to this island via a sea of ice floes.
Cease talking to me, you abominable pirates!
So the winter sky I saw from the ship...
was real after all.
The burning island Luffy and the others went to is an arctic island from the other side.
Basically, we've been taken to the arctic side!
Though if we want to know who brought us here, and why,
we'll have to get out of this room and see for ourselves.
But Nami-san, the door is solid.
It doesn't look like we'll be able to...
Out of my way!
I've got a full tank of cola!
Hey! Hey, hey, wait a second!
It's open. Let's get out.
I see that weird body isn't just for show.
I wanna shoot beams too!
So what are you gonna do?
You'd want to escape with us if we weren't pirates, right?
Silence! Be on your way, pirate!
There's no way for you to escape alone without a body.
What are you doing?!
Am I right, samurai of the Wano Kingdom?!
He's a samurai?!
This topknot is a hairstyle unique to the Wano Kingdom.
Does that mean that the murderous samurai they mentioned on the Snail-Phone was him?!
Scary!
I heard a blast from over here!
Hurry!
Could it be the pirates we captured?
Sanji-kun, hurry! They're coming for us!
We came here after receiving an emergency signal from someone you attacked, samurai!
Sanji, let's hurry!
Just leave that scary samurai behind!
I would never bring dishonor upon myself by committing murder!
I came to this island to rescue my son!
I will kill all who get in my way!
There they are!
Fire! Don't let them get away!
Stop right there! I'll take you on!
How did they get out?!
Contact Master immediately!
Who are they?!
Sanji-kun!
You brought him with you?!
He's dangerous!
You can blame me if anything happens!
There's a door!
Who are you?
What?!
Gigantic... children?
C-Children?!
What's going on here?!
Who are these kids?
Perhaps this is some sort of nursery?
They're absolutely huge. Are they giants?
Did we drop anchor at an island of giants?
But there are some smaller kids too...
Then, maybe this facility
doesn't discriminate between races?
I don't see any adults, though.
Hey, who are you?
I don't know them...
Ah, could you be the frozen people?
Did you make it out?!
Frozen?
What's she talking about?
You're a robot!
W-What?!
It's a robot!
So cool!
I love robots!
They're the best!
What do you mean, best?
Sanji-kun?!
Robot! Robot! Robot!
Oh my, you...
like armored me that much?!
Hey, what did she mean by frozen people?
Oh, look! It's a stuffed animal!
What?
A stuffed raccoon dog!
I'm a reindeer!
How cute!
Help me!
I want one!
Franky is ridiculously popular with these kids!
Swirly eyebrows!
Shut up, you damn brat!
You're right!
I say, all of you!
Do any of you know of a child named Momonosuke?!
He is a young man, he is!
Scary!
The head spoke!
Run!
Hey, you guys! Can you tell us-
Wait!
Shut up, idiot! We can't ask them anything!
You're just scaring them whenever you speak!
The door to Biscuits Room is open!
Here they come!
Anyway, let's just get to the far side of the room!
It must be the pirates from before.
Don't let them escape!
What kind of facility is this?!
Please tell me!
I seek a child named Momonosuke!
Just stop talking!
A woman raised her hand against me!
This is a shame for a warrior, it is!
I want to slice open my belly!
Go ahead! You're getting on my nerves,
you chauvinist pig!
Damn escapees!
You're not getting out of here!
Wait!
Calm down. Guns and explosives are forbidden here.
We can't use anything stronger than gas bullets.
If we hit the children, we'll answer to the Master!
Alright, children, out of the way.
Out of the way!
That's dangerous!
Hey, Robot-san.
You aren't fom this island, are you?
Of course not. But, boy... I am a cybor-
Do you have a ship?
Of course we do! Our Sunny is the world's-
Save us!
What does he mean?
Please, save us!
What do you mean, save you?
This isn't a nursery?!
We're not sick any more!
We're all fine!
Sick? With what disease?
Those damn brats!
Please, wait!
Let us out of here!
Please, Lady! Help us!
Now, wait up, children!
Sorry... we're being chased, so...
What's going on?!
Hey, let's take them with us!
Idiot! We don't even know where to go ourselves!
What good would come
from bringing all those kids along?!
But why...
am I feeling so sad?!
In that case...
come save us later!
I know, even though
I haven't gone outside the building!
This island is empty, right?!
There's no town here and no people!
That's why nobody has come to help us!
I wanna see Mommy and Daddy!
Lady! Please come back!
Come back to save us!
Let's help these children!
What are you saying, Nami-san?! There's no reason to do that!
They even said they were sick! This might be a hospital!
We only just met them,
and we don't know what's going on here!
It's not like we're a charity that rescues children!
Do you think I don't know that?
But when children are crying for me to save them...
how can I turn my back on them?!
Lady!
Quickly, they're getting away!
Those kids are in the way!
Who cares?! Kill them aswell!
But Master will...
It's still better than letting them get away!
Sanji-kun!
Swirly bro!
Awesome!
That man...
is incredibly skilled!
Damn it!
Raccoon Dog-chan!
A rocket punch!
T-They're...
not running away anymore!
When Nami-san is kind... (only ever to children)...
she is truly wonderful!
I'm falling for her all over again!
Chopper. You go on ahead with Nami-san.
Sure, leave it to me!
Hey, kids! Follow the beautiful lady and the Kung Fu raccoon dog!
I'll hold back the pursuers!
But don't get the wrong idea!
I'm only responding
to the longing in Nami-san's heart to save you.
If anything,
I hate you for stealing Nami-san's affection!
Thanks, swirly bro!
Shut it, you damn brat!
Now, bring it!
I see. This door can absorb any impact, and yet...
Master!
...there are burn-marks.
Just who are those people?
I thought he was the only one with the technology to make lasers.
This reminds me of that despicable Vegapunk's Pacifista!
You still haven't captured the escapees?
They should have them cornered in the Biscuit Room by now.
The Biscuit Room?
Master, are you there?!
Yes, I am here.
A warship from G-5 is approaching the Northwest side of the island!
A warship?! Drive it off at any cost!
Release a large volume of poison gas!
Just don't kill them. If you do, the Government might figure out what we're up to.
Roger!
What?! Nami and the others are gone?!
Punk Hazard Island, The Burning Lands
You mean you're alone?!
And when you woke up, there was snow and ice all around you?
Indeed!
I was so surprised! I felt like a bone in a thunderstorm!
Huh?
No wait, like thunder in a duckstorm...
No, a duck in a bonestorm?
Well, whatever!
Ah, pardon me!
Were they trying to steal the cargo on the Sunny? Who were they?
Well, I really don't...
By the way,
who are you fellows?
I took them out before I got a chance to ask.
They all appear to be wearing some kind of gas masks.
Gas masks? Perhaps they used some sort of sleeping gas?
And then those people took the Sunny to the opposite side of the island.
Dammit, I lost!
You sure are fast!
You did quite well yourself!
Alright, let's go again!
No matter how many times you try-
Hello?
What are you goofing around for?
Well, I just can't find them.
Are there really intruders here?
All I've found are a funny guy with talking hind-legs and his group.
He is the intruder!
Come on! Let's keep going!
Where are Nami-san and the others?
Since they didn't leave behind a message,
it seems likely they were taken somewhere.
I get it! Since you're a skeleton,
they must have assumed you were just a corpse!
I see, so that's why I was left behind! Such luck!
The enemy thinks they've captured all of us.
Are there any buildings or traces of people nearby?
Oh, Robin-san, your reasoning is so sharp. It's like you can see everything!
There is...
a building.
A truly massive one!
It doesn't look like a restaurant.
Brook, we're hurrying over there, so wait for us.
Robin-san?
When you get here, may I see your-
Is our enemy someone from the Government?
Who knows? Let's hope they're at least human.
I mean, so far we've seen...
a fire-breathing dragon,
a half-man,
and a bird-lady!
And then there's that centaur Luffy just befr-
Now listen here!
What?! What's gotten into you?!
You...
I let my guard down. I thought you were on my side.
Why can't I be?
We're already friends, so don't attack me!
Die, intruder!
There's another one!
Bellflower
A leopard and a giraffe, huh?
Looks like there are all kinds of centaurs. How fun!
They're fictional horses!
Their very existence is bizarre!
Look at this Baby Snail-Phone! It's got "CC" written on it!
They're not wild centaurs.
It must be some sort of organization!
In any case, even if we do return to the fiery ocean, the Sunny won't be there.
We've got no choice but to head for the arctic lands.
Nami, Sanji, Franky and Chopper have all gone missing!
They've most likely been kidnapped.
I just hope they haven't been shot full of holes by a rifle.
Cut that out!
It'd have been faster if we just dropped anchor on the other side of the island!
But then we wouldn't have been able to eat that dragon meat or meet Legson!
And who is Legson?
Oh, that's my back legs' name!
Alright, let's go! We're changing our objective!
Head for the frozen lands to rescue our crewmates!
I wonder if anyone will be selling winter clothing along the way.
If we go there dressed like this, we'll seriously die.
What do we do?
Vice-admiral Smoker! We can't!
The Northwestern Shore
I-I can't breathe!
Gas is still leaking out!
Ever since that damn Vegapunk's weapon experiments failed four years ago...
the whole island's gone rotten!
More importantly, I can't see Straw Hat Luffy's pirate ship anywhere!
There's no way anyone would come ashore with this much poisonous gas around.
That's not it.
It's unnatural for there to be this much gas.
What do you mean?
Two years ago, this was just a deserted island, with no fire or ice on it.
Surprisingly enough, most of the toxic materials had dissipated by then.
That's why Akainu and Aokiji...
chose Punk Hazard...
as the site of their duel.
A battle fierce enough to alter the climate!